http://www.wcaboise.org/about-us/reports-policies/privacy-policy/

24-hour Domestic Violence Hotline: 208.343.7025
|
24-hour Rape Crisis Hotline: 208.345.7273 (RAPE)Women's and Children's AllianceSafety, healing and freedom from domestic abuse and sexual assault. Donate Today!
Twitter
Facebook
Youtube
Escape
Menu  HomeGet Help
Is it Really Abuse?Domestic Abuse and Sexual Assault HotlinesCase ManagementFinancial EmpowermentEmergency and Transitional ShelterSafety PlanningTherapy & SupportCourt AdvocacyRape Crisis AdvocacyResources
Self-HelpGeneral InformationPopulation & CultureHelp Someone You Care AboutHealthy Relationships
Español
Give Support
Financial Support
EndowmentCorporate PillarsGrantsHope SocietyHost a Fundraising EventMarketing Materials
In-Kind DonationsHost a Donation DriveWish ListThe Shop
Get Involved
Education & Outreach
PSA Contest
AmbassadorsIf These Walls Could Talk TourVolunteer
Group Volunteer ProjectsVolunteer Opportunities
News & Events
NewsPress ReleasesEvents
Healing Begins with HopeThe Clothesline ProjectDenim DayDomestic Violence Awareness MonthIdaho Gives DaySueB 5K/10KTeen Dating Violence Awareness MonthPSA ContestTribute to Women and Industry
Joyce Stein Award
Calendar of EventsNewsletter
About Us
Our HistoryStatisticsAbout Sexual AssaultAbout Domestic AbuseStaffBoard of DirectorsCareersContact UsReports & Policies
Annual ReportsPrivacy PolicyEqual Opportunity PolicySocial Media Policy
Privacy Policy
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the The Women’s and Children’s Alliance Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Women’s and Children’s Alliance website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. View our  Client Notice of Privacy Practices.
Collection of your Personal Information
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. The Women’s and Children’s Alliance also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.
There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by The Women’s and Children’s Alliance. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by The Women’s and Children’s Alliance for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the The Women’s and Children’s Alliance Web site.
Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through The Women’s and Children’s Alliance public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: The Women’s and Children’s Alliance does not read any of your private online communications.
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from The Women’s and Children’s Alliance so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. The Women’s and Children’s Alliance is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on Web sites outside of the The Women’s and Children’s Alliance and The Women’s and Children’s Alliance family of Web sites.
Use of your Personal Information
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance collects and uses your personal information to operate the The Women’s and Children’s Alliance Web site and deliver the services you have requested. The Women’s and Children’s Alliance also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from The Women’s and Children’s Alliance and its affiliates. The Women’s and Children’s Alliance may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. The Women’s and Children’s Alliance may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, The Women’s and Children’s Alliance may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to The Women’s and Children’s Alliance, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within The Women’s and Children’s Alliance, in order to determine what The Women’s and Children’s Alliance services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within The Women’s and Children’s Alliance to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on The Women’s and Children’s Alliance or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of The Women’s and Children’s Alliance; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of The Women’s and Children’s Alliance, or the public.
Use of Cookies
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.
One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize The Women’s and Children’s Alliance pages, or register with The Women’s and Children’s Alliance site or services, a cookie helps The Women’s and Children’s Alliance to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same The Women’s and Children’s Alliance Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the The Women’s and Children’s Alliance features that you customized.
You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the The Women’s and Children’s Alliance services or Web sites you visit.
Security of your Personal Information
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. The Women’s and Children’s Alliance secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.
Changes to this Statement
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. The
Women’s and Children’s Alliance encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how The Women’s and Children’s Alliance is protecting your information.
Contact Information
The Women’s and Children’s Alliance welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that The Women’s and Children’s Alliance has not adhered to this Statement, please contact The Women’s and Children’s Alliance at info@wcaboise.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
Get Help
Volunteer
News & Events
Give Support
Contact Us
Latest Post
The BeaLine: November 2020
Back to Blog >> … » Read More
The WCA provides services to ALL who have experienced domestic abuse and/or sexual assault regardless of race, color, religion, gender, gender expression, age, national origin, marital status, or sexual orientation.
Contact Us
Women's and Children's Alliance
720 West Washington St.
Corporate PillarsBack To Top© 2020 Women's and Children's Alliance | Privacy Policy | Equal Opportunity Policies
